<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts | UMSBCC</title>
    <link>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Posts</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2023 UM Statistics &amp; Biostatistics Computing Club</copyright>
    <image>
      <url>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/img/icon_512.png</url>
      <title>Posts</title>
      <link>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biostatistics Expansion &amp; Slack Workspace</title>
      <link>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2022 10:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Computing Club is proud to announce its expansion to the Biostatistcs department! The Club will now hold joint meetings with PhD students from both the Statistics &amp;amp; Biostatistics department. With this change, we hope to draw even more students to share their computing knowledge. We would like to use this opportunity to welcome &lt;a href=&#34;https://benbren.github.io/cv/&#34;&gt;Ben Brennan&lt;/a&gt;, who will join the organizing committee!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Club meetings will start back with the 2023 Winter semester. Until then, we invite you to join the &lt;a href=&#34;https://mcommunity.umich.edu/#group:Computing%20Club&#34;&gt;Mcommunity&lt;/a&gt; which will automatically add you the our new &lt;strong&gt;Slack workspace&lt;/strong&gt;. This new workspace is primarily a platform for students to ask for computing help and share things with each other.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We will soon send an &lt;strong&gt;invitation to present&lt;/strong&gt; to gather a list of potential presenters and topics!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the Computing club&#39;s new website</title>
      <link>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 22:06:16 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>https://UMichStatistics.github.io/ComputingClub/post/welcome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the recent creation of the Statistics Computing Club, having a platform to share news, contents and resources was a priority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site is functionnal but still under construction, so please &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/UMichStatistics/ComputingClub/issues&#34;&gt;report issues&lt;/a&gt; to the GitHub repository to help us improve the site. Also, your comments and suggestions are more than welcome, so feel free to &lt;a href=&#34;#contact&#34;&gt;contact&lt;/a&gt; us!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Committee is still looking for presenters for this fall&amp;rsquo;s meetings. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to be an expert of the topic you&amp;rsquo;ll present; providing exposure to a tool you find useful, to a package you think may help others or to some research methodology may be relevant to many other members! If you feel like presenting, we invite you to complete this &lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/XMtKfjhJTuaaHdLU7&#34;&gt;form&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
